Guide to the Cause Marketing Forum. Halo Awards Records, 2002-2012 and undated RL.11128
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- 2009, 7
  - Transactional, 2009; 65
    - Aeropostale/Do Something: Teens for Jeans, 2009 (Box 54)
    - AT&T/U.S. Olympic Committee: Team USA Soundtrack, 2009 (Box 54)
    - Boston Market/Give Kids the World: Katie's Kitchen, 2009 (Box 54)
    - Children's Miracle Network Spring Miracle Balloon Campaign, 2009 (Box 54)
    - Coca-Cola (Vault)/United Service Organization (USO): Honoring the Uniform, Calling for Support, 2009; 2 folders (Box 54)
    - Lindt Sprungli/Autism Speaks: Have You Heard, 2009 (Box 54)
    - Macy's/Make-a-Wish Foundation: A Million Reasons to Believe, 2009; 2 folders (Box 54)
    - Orkin/United Nations Foundation: Nothing but Nets (malaria), 2009 (Box 54)
    - Sprint/Nature Conservancy: Samsung Reclaim (cell phone made from recycled parts), 2009; 2 folders (Box 54)
    - Subaru/Carmichael Lynch/National Wildlife Federation: Share the Love, 2009 (Box 55)
    - Toys R Us/Autism Speaks: Solving the Autism Puzzle, 2009 (Box 55)
    - Toys R Us/Autism Speaks: Solving the Autism Puzzle--Help Solve the Puzzle, 2009 (Box OV5)
    - United Airlines/American Cancer Society: Kenny HugYou--Send a Child's Spirit Soaring, 2009 (Box 55)
  - Unidentified Category, 2009; 66
    - American Express/Share Our Strength: No Kid Hungry, 2009 (Box 55)
- 2010, 8
  - Digital Marketing, 2010; 67
    - Clorox (Clean Up)/Center for Courageous Kids: Power a Bright Future Grant Program, 2010 (Box 55)
    - General Mills/Grace House: I 3 BKFST, 2010; 2 folders (Box 55)
    - General Mills/Komen for the Cure: Pink Together, 2010 (Box 55)
    - Kohl's Department Stores: Kohl's Cares $10 Million Contest, 2010 (Box 55)
    - Kohl's Department Stores: Kohl's Cares, 2010 (Box OV3)
    - Procter & Gamble Children's Safe Drinking Water Program: P, 2010 (Box 55)
    - Procter & Gamble/USO: Road to Reunion, 2010 (Box 55)
    - Sonic/Donors Choice: Limeades for Learning, 2010 (Box 55)
    - Sonic/Donors Choice: Limeades for Learning, 2010 (Box 56)
    - Toys R Us/Multiple nonprofits: Join Shaq Give Back, 2010 (Box 56)
    - Yahoo!/Multiple nonprofits: You In?, 2010 (Box 56)
  - Environmental/Animal, 2010; 68
    - Frito-Lay: Sun Chips Building a Pre-eminent Green Brand, 2010 (Box 56)
    - Frito-Lay: Sun Chips Building a Pre-eminent Green Brand (compostable bag), 2010 (Box OV8)
    - Royal Bank of Canada (RBC): RBC Blue Water Project, 2010 (Box 56)
    - TD Bank Group/TD Friends of the Environment Foundation: TD Go Green Challenge, 2010 (Box 56)
  - Event, 2010; 69
    - Conde Nast Publications/Komen for the Cure: Rally for the Cure, 2010; 2 folders (Box 56)
    - Macy's/Make-a-Wish Foundation: National Believe Day, 2010 (Box 56)
  - Health-Related, 2010; 70
    - A&E Network/National Council on Alcohol and Drug Dependency (NCADD): Recovery Project, 2010 (Box 56)
    - A&E Network/Salvation Army: Intervention Town Hall, 2010 (Box 56)
    - General Mills/Feeding America: Pound for Pound Challenge, 2010 (Box 56)
    - Hyundai: Hyundai Hope on Wheels, 2010 (Box 56)
    - Jiffy Lube/American Heart Association: Maintenance Partners for Life, 2010 (Box 56)
    - Pepsi (Propel)/Breast Cancer Connections: Hope Propelled, 2010 (Box 57)
    - Phonak (Switzerland): Hear the World, 2010 (Box 57)
  - Joint Message, 2010; 71
    - Children's Miracle Network: Give Miracles, 2010 (Box 57)
    - ConAgra Foods/Feeding America: Child Hunger Ends Here, 2010 (Box 57)
    - Jones Apparel Group: Jones NY in the Classroom, 2010 (Box 57)
    - Kohl's Department Stores/Multiple nonprofits: Kohl's Women's Health/Breast Cancer Initiative, 2010 (Box 57)
    - Liberty Mutual/ITN America: National Conversation Drive, 2010 (Box 57)
  - Multiple Categories, 2010; 72
    - Chivas Regal (Pernod Ricard)/Hispanic Foundation: Espiritu de Progreso Latino, 2010 (Box 57)
    - CNN/YMCA: CNN Fit Nation, 2010 (Box 57)
    - Coca-Cola/California State Parks: Reforest California--Join the Million Tree Challenge, 2010 (Box 57)
    - Field Trip Factory/H-E-Buddy: H-E-B's Be a Healthy Buddy, 2010 (Box 57)
    - General Mills/Box Tops for Education: Power of 1, 2010 (Box 57)
    - Hasbro/Multiple nonprofits: Project Zambi, 2010 (Box 57)
    - Iams/Helen Woodward Animal Center: Iams Home 4 the Holidays, 2010; 2 folders (Box 57)
    - Iams/Helen Woodward Animal Center: Iams Home 4 the Holidays, 2010 (Box 58)
    - Kraft Foods/Feeding America: Huddle to Fight Hunger, 2010 (Box 58)
    - National Down's Syndrome Society (NDSS): My Great Story, 2010; 3 folders (Box 58)
    - Reckitt Benckiser/Dollar General/Literacy Foundation: Improving Lives, 2010 (Box 58)
    - United Healthcare/Sesame Workshop: Food for Thought--Eating Well on a Budget, 2010 (Box 58)
  - National/Local Integration, 2010; 73
    - Ford/Komen for the Cure: Warriors in Pink, 2010 (Box 58)
    - New Balance/Komen for the Cure, 2010 (Box 58)
    - New Balance/Komen for the Cure, 2010 (Box 59)
    - Staples/Do Something: Do Something 101 School Supply Drive, 2010 (Box 59)
    - Weight Watchers/Share Our Strength: Lose for Good Campaign, 2010 (Box 59)
  - Print Creative, 2010; 74
    - LEC: The Angel Band Project, 2010 (Box OV5)
  - Social Service/Educational, 2010; 75
    - A&E Television/Vet Dogs: Take a Veteran to School Day, 2010 (Box 59)
    - H&R Block/DECA: Dollars and Sense, 2010; 2 folders (Box 59)
    - History Channel/America's Vet Dogs: Take a Veteran to School Day, 2010 (Box 59)
    - Sonic/Donors Choice: Limeades for Learning, 2010; 2 folders (Box 59)
    - Toys R Us/Multiple nonprofits: Safety Leadership Program--Focus on Baby Safety, 2010 (Box 60)
  - Transactional, 2010; 76
    - Bing (Microsoft)/Donors Choose: Our School Needs, 2010 (Box 60)
    - Bing (Microsoft)/Donors Choose: Teacher Appreciation, 2010 (Box 60)
    - Burlington Coat Factory/One Warm Coat: Warm Coats and Warm Hearts, 2010 (Box 60)
    - Campbell Soup/National Future Farmers of America (FFA) Foundation: Campbell Soup Company Grows Support for Agricultural Education, 2010 (Box 60)
    - Chili's/St. Jude Children's Research Hospital: Create-a-Pepper, 2010 (Box 60)
    - eBay/MissionFish: Shop, Sell and Donate for a Good Cause, 2010 (Box 60)
    - Payless ShoeSource/Nature Conservancy: Payless Helps the Nature Conservancy Plant a Billion Trees (Zoe Zac launch), 2010 (Box 60)
    - Sonic/Donors Choice: Limeades for Learning, 2010 (Box 60)
    - Sonic/Donors Choice: Limeades for Learning, 2010 (Box 61)
    - Tastefully Simple/Share Our Strength: Share Our Hope, Share Our Strength, 2010 (Box 61)
    - Telus (Canada)/Abbotsford Hospice Society: Community Telus TV Campaign, 2010 (Box 61)
    - Toys R Us/Save the Children: Bundled in Hope--Helping Provide Blankets for Babies in Need, 2010 (Box 61)
  - Video Creative, 2010; 77
    - Honeywell/Multiple nonprofits: Nobel Laureate Lecture Series--Inspiring the Next Generation of Scientists Today, 2010 (Box 61)
    - VSP Vision Care/American Diabetes Association: Stop Diabetes, 2010 (Box 61)
- 2011, 9
  - Digital Marketing, 2011; 78
    - Aviva Canada: Idea Couture, 2011 (Box 61)
    - Grain Foods Foundation/Share Our Strengths: The Bread Art Project, 2011 (Box 61)
    - Microsoft/American Red Cross: In-Game Advertising Campaign for Haiti and Chile Relief, 2011 (Box 61)
    - Outback Steakhouse: Thanks for Giving, 2011 (Box 61)
    - Sonic/Donors Choice: Limeades for Learning, 2011 (Box 61)
    - State Farm/Major League Baseball: Go to Bat, 2011 (Box 61)
    - Telus (Canada): Go Pink Facebook Campaign, 2011 (Box 61)
  - Environmental/Animal, 2011; 79
    - Kohl's Department Stores: National Volunteers Go Green, 2011 (Box 61)
    - Kraft Foods/Lilly Pulitzer/World Wildlife Federation, 2011 (Box 61)
    - Kraft Foods/Lilly Pulitzer/World Wildlife Federation, 2011 (Box OV5)
    - Procter & Gamble: P&G Future Friendly--Making Conservation Second Nature, 2011 (Box 61)
    - Scott's Miracle-Gro/Keep America Beautiful: Give Back to Gro, 2011 (Box 62)
    - Walt Disney/Multiple nonprofits: Disney Friends for Change Project Green, 2011 (Box 62)
    - Walt Disney/Nature Conservancy: Disneynature Oceans--See Oceans Save Oceans, 2011 (Box 62)
  - Event, 2011; 80
    - Cheesecake Factory/Feeding America: Share Your Voice, 2011 (Box 62)
    - CVS Caremark/Easter Seals: Walk with Me, 2011 (Box 62)
    - Dallas Moustace/Movember, 2011 (Box 62)
    - Hyundai Hope on Wheels, 2011 (Box 62)
    - Kohl's Department Stores: National Volunteers Go Green, 2011 (Box 62)
    - Kohl's Department Stores/Komen for the Cure: Blanket Milwaukee Pink, 2011 (Box 62)
    - Lockheed-Martin/Marine Toys for Tots Foundation: Blue Angels on a Mission, 2011 (Box 62)
    - Macy's/March of Dimes: Shop for a Cause, 2011 (Box 62)
    - OfficeMax/Adopt-a-Classroom: Teacher Goes the Extra Mile for His Students, 2011 (Box 62)
    - Papa Murphy's/Children's Cancer Association: Hearts of Joy, 2011 (Box 62)
    - World Vision: End Malaria, 2011 (Box 62)
  - Health-Related, 2011; 81
    - Cartoon Network: Move It Movement, 2011 (Box 62)
    - CYBEX/Breast Cancer Reesearch Foundation: CYBEX Pink Ribbon Run, 2011 (Box 62)
    - Georgia-Pacific: Spread Wellness, 2011; 2 folders (Box 62)
    - ITT/Multiple nonprofits: ITT Watermark, 2011 (Box 63)
    - ITT/Multiple nonprofits: ITT Watermark, 2011 (Box OV3)
    - Kohl's Department Stores: Kohl's Healthy Kids, 2011 (Box 63)
    - Kohl's Department Stores/Multiple nonprofits: Kohl's Women's Health/Breast Cancer Initiative, 2011 (Box 63)
    - Telus: Go Pink, 2011 (Box 63)
    - Toys R Us/Autism Speaks: Solving the Autism Puzzle, 2011 (Box OV5)
    - Vemma Nutrition/Multiple nonprofits: VemmaNext Helping Now Project, 2011 (Box 63)
    - Wal-Mart (Sam's Club)/Children's Miracle Network: Champions, 2011 (Box 63)
    - Walton Isaacson/ONE: Bellies (children with HIV), 2011 (Box 63)
    - World Vision: End Malaria, 2011 (Box 63)
  - Message-focused Campaign, 2011; 82
    - Clorox/American Red Cross: Emergency Preparedness Awareness, 2011 (Box 63)
    - Glad Products/Cookies for Kids' Cancer: Glad to Give Be a Good Cookie, 2011 (Box 63)
    - Hyundai Hope on Wheels Helping Kids Fight Cancer, 2011 (Box 63)
    - Scholastic Media/American Family Institute/Points of Light: Clifford the Dog Be Big! Campaign, 2011; 4 folders (Box 64)
    - Western Union/Multiple nonprofits: 50 Days of Giving, 2011 (Box 64)
    - World Vision: End Malaria, 2011 (Box 64)
  - Multiple Categories, 2011; 83
    - Avon/Nature Conservancy: Hello Green Tomorrow, 2011 (Box 64)
    - Campbell Soup/Family First/All Pro Dad: Chunky Soup All Pro Dad Pledge, 2011 (Box 65)
    - ConAgra Foods/Food Network/Share Our Strength: No Kid Hungry, 2011 (Box 65)
    - General Mills/Grace House: I 3 BKFST, 2011; 2 folders (Box 65)
    - International Justice Mission: Five Weeks for Freedom, 2011; 2 folders (Box 65)
    - OfficeMax/Adopt-a-Classroom: A Day Made Better 2010, 2011 (Box OV1)
    - OneUpWeb/Traverse City West Band Program: Step and Close, 2011 (Box 65)
    - Penguin Group/Pearson Foundation: We Give Books, 2011 (Box 65)
    - Procter & Gamble (Downy)/Quilts for Kids/Children's Miracle Network: Downy Touch of Comfort, 2011 (Box 65)
    - Procter & Gamble (PUR filters)/Children's Safe Drinking Water: PUR the Summit on the Summit Program, 2011 (Box 65)
  - Print Creative, 2011; 84
    - Delta Airlines/Children's Miracle Network: Turning Sky Miles into Miracles, 2011 (Box 65)
    - Procter & Gamble/Wal-Mart/United Service Organizations (USO): Operation Family Connect, 2011 (Box 65)
  - Social Service/Educational, 2011; 85
    - Cartoon Network: Stop Bullying, Speak Up, 2011 (Box 65)
    - HouseLogic/National Association of Realtors/USA Cares: Operation Home Relief, 2011 (Box 65)
    - Kohl's Department Stores: Kids Who Care Scholarship Program, 2011 (Box 66)
    - Kohl's Department Stores/Milwaukee Art Museum: Kohl's and Milwaukee Art Museum, 2011 (Box 66)
    - Liberty Mutual/ITN America: National Conversation Drive, 2011 (Box 66)
    - Men's WearHouse/Multiple nonprofits: Attack the Mancession with National Suit Drive, 2011 (Box OV11)
    - Pearson/Jumpstart: Jumpstart's Read for the Record, 2011 (Box 66)
    - Reckitt Benckiser/Dollar General/Literacy Foundation: Literacy Rocks!, 2011 (Box 66)
    - Time Warner Cable/FIRST/CSAS: Connect a Million Minds, 2011; 2 folders (Box 66)
    - Time Warner Cable/FIRST/CSAS: Connect a Million Minds, 2011 (Box OV1)
    - Toys R Us/Kids in Danger: Product Safety Vigilance Program, 2011 (Box 66)
    - Viacom/Get Schooled Foundation: Get Schooled National Challenge and Tour, 2011 (Box 66)
    - Walton Isaacson/ONE: Bellies (children with HIV), 2011 (Box 66)
    - Washington Redskins Charitable Foundation/Marine Toys for Tots: Touchdown for Tots, 2011 (Box 66)
  - Transactional, 2011; 86
    - American Express/Whole Foods Market/Share Our Strength: No Kid Hungry, 2011 (Box 66)
    - Ann Taylor Stores/Breast Cancer Research Foundation: Ann Cares, Loft Cares, 2011 (Box 66)
    - Bulgari/Save the Children: Bulgari for Children's Education, 2011 (Box 66)
    - Capital One/Network for Good: Haiti Relief, 2011 (Box 66)
    - Chevron/Donors Choose: Fuel Your School, An Energy for Learning Initiative, 2011 (Box 67)
    - Choice Hotels/Rebuilding Together: Signature Music for Signature Causes, 2011 (Box 67)
    - CVS Caremark/World Wildlife Fund: Green Bag Tag Program, 2011 (Box 67)
    - Hyundai Hope on Wheels, 2011 (Box 67)
    - Kohl's Department Stores: Kohl's Cares Cause Merchandise, 2011 (Box 67)
    - Macy's/American Heart Association: Wear Red Sale, 2011 (Box 67)
    - Sephora/Skin Cancer Foundation: Sephora Sun Safety Kit, 2011 (Box 67)
    - Syngenta Crop Protection (Halex GT)/Feeding America: Weeding Out Hunger, 2011 (Box 67)
    - Toys R Us/UNICEF/Kids Helping Kids: Trick or Treat, 2011 (Box 67)
    - Walgreen/Children's Hospital Foundation: Campaign for the Children's Hospital, 2011 (Box 67)
  - Video Creative, 2011; 87
    - Food Network/Big Picture Group/Share Our Strength: No Kid Hungry, 2011 (Box 67)
    - ICE Worldwide/Friends Forever: Did You Know...?, 2011 (Box 67)
    - Kohl's Department Stores/American Cancer Society: Live Pink Ribbon, 2011 (Box 67)
    - Old Navy/United Service Organizations (USO): Operation Phone Home, 2011 (Box 67)
    - Procter & Gamble/USO/Wal-Mart Campaign, 2011 (Box 67)
    - Procter & Gamble/Wal-Mart/United Service Organizations (USO): Operation Family Connect, 2011 (Box 67)
    - TakePart/sOccket, 2011 (Box 67)
    - Time Warner Cable/FIRST/CSAS: Connect a Million Minds, 2011 (Box 67)
    - Walton Isaacson/ONE: Bellies (children with HIV), 2011 (Box 67)
- 2012, 10
  - Digital Marketing, 2012; 88
    - CDW/Multiple nonprofits: CDW Holiday Program, 2012 (Box 67)
    - Charles Schwab/Schwab Community Services/Multiple nonprofits: Schwab Gives, 2012 (Box 67)
    - Coca-Cola/World Wildlife Fund: Arctic Home, 2012 (Box 67)
    - Gillette/USO: Give Words, Send Love Facebook Promotion, 2012 (Box 68)
    - Hanes/Salvation Army: Hanes' Virtual Sock Drive, 2012 (Box 68)
    - Kohl's/Feeding America/Marine Toys for Tots: Love to Give, Happy to Save Facebook Contest, 2012 (Box 68)
    - Kohl's/Komen for the Cure: Every Ribbon Tells a Story, 2012 (Box 68)
    - LivingSocial/Marine Toys for Tots: Helping Local Kids in Need, 2012 (Box 68)
    - Macy's/Multiple nonprofits: Thank a Mom Movement, 2012 (Box 68)
    - Procter & Gamble (Pepto-Bismol)/Feeding America: Pepto-Bismol Throws a Feast for All, 2012 (Box 68)
    - Toys R Us/Autism Speaks: Be a Hero for Autism, 2012 (Box 68)
    - Whirlpool (Maytag)/Boys and Girls Clubs of America: Faces of Dependability, 2012 (Box 68)
  - Environmental/Animal, 2012; 89
    - Barefoot Wine/Surfrider Project: Barefoot Wine Beach Rescue Project, 2012 (Box 68)
    - Kohl's National Go Green Initiative, 2012 (Box 68)
    - Walt Disney/World Wildlife Fund: Disney Friends for Change, 2012 (Box 68)
  - Event, 2012; 90
    - Frito-Lay (Tostitos)/Big Brothers and Big Sisters: Fiesta in the Square, 2012 (Box 68)
    - General Mills (Yoplait)/Komen for the Cure: Save Lids to Save Lives Pink House Event, 2012 (Box 68)
    - Great Wolf Lodge/Big Brothers and Big Sisters: 2nd Annual Waterslide-a-Thon, 2012 (Box 68)
    - Kohl's/Komen for the Cure: Southeast Wisconsin Race for the Cure, 2012 (Box 68)
    - Maxwell House/Rebuilding Together: Drop of Good the Maxwell House Community Project, 2012 (Box 68)
    - Maxwell House/Rebuilding Together: Drop of Good the Maxwell House Community Project, 2012 (Box 69)
    - Procter & Gamble (Bounty)/Multiple nonprofit: We Love Our School, 2012; 2 folders (Box 69)
    - The French Will Never Forget: 9/11 Tribute, 2012 (Box 69)
    - Toys R Us/Alex's Lemonade Stand Foundation: Fight Childhood Cancer One Cup at a Time, 2012 (Box 69)
    - United Service Organizations (USO): Military Bowl, 2012 (Box 69)
    - Walgreens/Komen for the Cure: Way to Well Commitment, 2012 (Box 69)
    - Walt Disney/World Wildlife Fund: Pirates of the Caribbean On Stranger Tides to Benefit Boys and Girls Clubs, 2012 (Box 69)
  - Health-Related, 2012; 91
    - AFLAC/AFLAC Cancer Center: Friends of a Feather--AFLAC's Commitment to Children with Cancer, 2012 (Box 69)
    - CIBC (Canadian Imperial Bank of Commerce)/Canadian Breast Cancer Foundation: Run for the Cure, 2012 (Box 69)
    - Kohl's Department Stores/American Cancer Society/Komen for the Cure: Kohl's Women's Health/Breast Cancer Initiative, 2012 (Box 69)
    - Kroger/Multiple nonprofits: Giving Hope a Hand, 2012 (Box 69)
    - NFL/American Cancer Society: A Crucial Catch--Annual Screening Saves Lives, 2012 (Box 69)
    - NFL Play 60, 2012 (Box 70)
    - Produce for Kids/Children's Miracle Network: Get Healthy Give Hope, 2012 (Box 70)
    - Sanofi Pasteur: Dishing with the Co-Stars (Inspiring Americans to support people living with diabetes), 2012 (Box 70)
    - Sanofi Pasteur/March of Dimes: Sounds of Pertussis/Race to Blanket America, 2012; 2 folders (Box 70)
    - SHARE/CHADD (Children and Adults with ADHD))/ADDA (Attention Deficit Disease Association): Own It, 2012 (Box 70)
    - Tempur-Pedic/Pancreatic Cancer Action Network: Hugs Back, 2012 (Box 70)
    - VSP Vision Care/Boys and Girls Clubs of America: VSP Eye Pledge, 2012 (Box 70)
  - Message-focused Campaign, 2012; 92
    - Bob Woodruff Foundation/Stand Up for Heroes: Makeovers for Military's Night Out, 2012 (Box 70)
    - Hickory Farms/Share Our Strength: No Kid Hungry, 2012 (Box 70)
    - Johnson & Johnson (Clean Clear)/United Nations Foundation Girl Up Campaign: Girl Up and Clean Clear Partnership, 2012 (Box 70)
    - Macy's/Reading is Fundamental: Be Book Smart, 2012 (Box 70)
    - NFL Play 60, 2012 (Box 70)
    - Scholastic Book Fairs/Matt Birk's Hike Foundation: Read and Rise, 2012 (Box 71)
    - Stream Energy/Captain Hope's Kids: Make 2012 a Year for Kids (Box 71)
    - Walgreen: Walk with Walgreen, 2012 (Box 71)
  - Multiple Categories, 2012; 93
    - American Cancer Society: First Anniversary of American Cancer Society's Choose Your Movement, 2012 (Box 71)
    - American Kidney Fund: Pair Up, 2012 (Box 71)
    - Bank of America/Feeding America: Gift for Opportunity Fund, 2012 (Box 71)
    - Capella University: Inspire Giving, 2012 (Box 71)
    - Coca-Cola/World Wildlife Fund: Arctic Home, 2012 (Box 71)
    - Ford/Komen for the Cure: Warriors in Pink, 2012 (Box 71)
    - Halogen TV/Soles 4 Souls, 2012 (Box 71)
    - History Channel/Vietnam Veterans Memorial Fund: Call for Photos, 2012 (Box 71)
    - Kellogg (Keebler)/American Red Cross: Be a Good Cookie, 2012 (Box 71)
    - Nature Valley/National Parks Conservation Association: Nature Valley National Parks Project, 2012 (Box 71)
    - Omega Watch/Orbis: A Shared Vision: Omega and Orbis, 2012 (Box 71)
    - Pearson Foundation/Hyatt/We Give Books/Chicago Public Schools: We Give Books--Read for Chicago Public Schools, 2012 (Box 72)
    - Rotary International: This Close, 2012 (Box 72)
    - Sears/Rebuilding Together: Heroes at Home A Hero's Song, 2012 (Box 72)
    - Sears/Rebuilding Together: Partnering to Rebuild Hero's Lives, 2012 (Box 72)
    - Southwest Airlines/Student Conservation Association: 40 Projects for 40 Years, 2012 (Box 72)
    - TakePart/Participant Media: How a Virus Changes the World, 2012 (Box 72)
    - Walgreen: Walk with Walgreen, 2012 (Box 72)
    - Walgreens/Multiple nonprofits: Arm Yourself with a Walgreens Flu Shot, 2012 (Box 72)
    - Zynga/Save the Children: Transforming the World Through Games, 2012 (Box 72)
  - Print Creative, 2012; 94
    - Harley-Davidson/United Service Organizations (USO): Honor the Brave, 2012 (Box 72)
    - New Balance/Komen for the Cure: Let's Make a Cure Happen, 2012 (Box 72)
  - Social Service/Educational, 2012; 95
    - Benjamin Moore/Multiple nonprofits: Color Care Across America, 2012 (Box 72)
    - Build-a-Bear Workshop: Huggable Heroes, 2012 (Box 72)
    - Cartoon Network: Stop Bullying, Speak Up, 2012; 2 folders (Box 72)
    - Duracell/National Volunteer Fire Council: Power Those Who Protect Us, 2012; 2 folders (Box 72)
    - JetBlue Airways/PBS Kids: Soar with Reading, 2012 (Box 73)
    - Kohl's/Zoological Society of Milwaukee: Wild Theater Program, 2012 (Box 73)
    - Motorola/Girl Scouts of America: Reality Check, 2012 (Box 73)
    - PetSmart Charities screen shots, 2012 (Box 73)
    - Procter & Gamble/Communities in Schools: P&G MyGive Inspiring Communities to Touch and Improve Lives, 2012 (Box 73)
    - Procter & Gamble/Special Olympics: P&G Thank You Mom, 2012 (Box 73)
    - Time Warner Cable/FIRST (For Inspiration and Recognition of Science and Technology): Build a Million Minds, 2012 (Box 73)
  - Transactional, 2012; 96
    - Aeropostale/Do Something: Teens for Jeans, 2012 (Box 73)
    - Chevron/Donors Choose: Fuel Your School, An Energy for Learning Initiative, 2012 (Box 73)
    - Coca-Cola/World Wildlife Fund: Arctic Home, 2012 (Box 73)
    - ConAgra Foods/Feeding America: Child Hunger Ends Here, 2012 (Box 73)
    - CVS/Pharmacy/ALS Therapy Alliance: Researching a Cure, 2012 (Box 73)
    - Great Wolf Lodge/Big Brothers and Big Sisters: Gingerbread Houses with a Heart for Charity, 2012 (Box 73)
    - Groupon/Donors Choose: Donors Choose, J.P. Morgan Chase and Groupon Partnership, 2012 (Box 73)
    - Kraft Foods/Food Bank Canada: Food for Families, 2012 (Box 73)
    - Kroger/USO: Honoring Our Heroes, 2012 (Box 73)
    - Oshkosh B'Gosh/Kids in Distressed Situations: Oshkosh Cranes for Kids, 2012 (Box 73)
    - Quidsi/American Red Cross: Refer-a-Friend Program, 2012 (Box 73)
    - Telus (Canada): Phones for Good, TV for Good, 2012 (Box 73)
  - Video Creative, 2012; 97
    - American Airlines/UNICEF: Change for Good Program, 2012 (Box 73)
    - Dermalogia/JoinFite, 2012 (Box 73)
    - Procter & Gamble (Pringles)/USO: Pringles Supports Our Troops A Little Taste of Home, 2012 (Box 73)
- Undated, 11
  - Social Service/Educational, Undated; 98
    - Virgin Mobile direct mailer, Undated (Box 73)
    - Stickers: Hefty Zoo Pals/Sports Pals; Pero Vegetables "5 a Day the Color Way", Undated (Box OV13)
- Audiovisual Materials, 2002-2012 and undated; 12
  - Originals, 2002-2012 and undated; 99
    - Real Talk, Real Answers Atlanta Program., 2007 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-001)
    - NMSS Meeting (edited), 2007 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-002)
    - Highmark Healthy High 5 Signature Partner Resource Guide, 2007 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-003)
    - Lung Cancer Alliance Media Campaign, undated (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-004)
    - Rally for the Cure, undated (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-005)
    - KPMG-RBI Volunteer Video, 2008 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-006)
    - KPMG-RBI Life Skills Training Powerpoint, 2008 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-007)
    - KPMG--The Face of RBI, 2008 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-008)
    - KPMG Steps to the Plate, 2008 (Box AV2, Dvd RL11030-DVD-009)